Damn it!
You fucking
piece of trash.
If it weren't for
your big fat mouth,
I'd already have
that trophy.
Ted.
It was all West.
Look,
so uh, we have a
beef between us.
Come join my team.
Help me win the
next championship.
Whatever you
want, you got it.
Don't you worry that
intentionally
injuring other players
is going to
get you expelled
by the league?
NFL rules
are for poor people.
Unless the
commissioner himself
is involved in this,
money can
fix anything.
Ted, you're
wasting your time
on this small team.
Come join me.
We'll build
a super team.
We'll win
every Super Bowl!
I'm gonna go
ahead and
politely decline
your offer.
But you know,
I think you need to
start figuring out
how you uh...
explain all that to
the commissioner.
Davis, considering
your egregious actions,
all teams under your ownership are suspended
immediately.
You are banned
from participating
in the NFL
in any capacity
and fined one hundred million dollars.
Come on, man.
A hundred
million dollars?
Ted, word with me.
You can fix this.
Tell him it's all just
a misunderstanding.
Just a joke.
I don't know.
Maybe you need to
figure out how
you're gonna pay
that hundred
million dollars too.
But you know, for
a rich guy like you,
that shouldn't
be a problem.
Right?
All right, boys,
get him out of here.
I'm tired of this.
Hey, hey, guys.
Chill.
Think about
what you're doing!
I can give you
every Super Bowl.
I'll give
you everything.
I'm sorry. Ted.
What are you doing?
Grace.
I got
the championship.
I've got the girl.
Now.
I think it's time for
my Christmas gift.
Ruling on the field.
Stands.